<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CalorieScope</string>
    <string name="Menu_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="Home">Home</string>
    <string name="News">News</string>
    <string name="Settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="About">About</string>
    <string name="Lets_Start">Let\'s Start</string>
    <string name="Walk"> Walk </string>
    <string name="Rest"> Rest </string>
    <string name="Clear"> Clear </string>
    <string name="Water">Water</string>
    <string name="Caffeine">Caffeine</string>
    <string name="PlusSymbol">+</string>
    <string name="numeral_0">0</string>
    <string name="Clear_Fluid_Intake"> Clear Fluid Intake </string>
    <string name="Retry">Retry</string>
    <string name="Save">Save</string>
    <string name="Load_Defaults">Load Defaults</string>
    <string name="Clear_App_Data">Clear App Data</string>
    <string name="User">User</string>
    <string name="Calculator">"Calculator"</string>
    <string name="title_bmi">BMI</string>
    <string name="title_whr">WHR</string>
    <string name="developed_by">Developed by Karanvir Singh</string>
    <string name="Github_Link">https://github.com/kvsjxd/CalorieScope</string>
    <string name="about_paragraph">We all know the popular saying health is wealth. The loss of health is a loss of all happiness. In
the present times people are busy in daily schedules and find no time to exercise therefore an app
called CalorieScope has been introduced which can keep track of the basic exercise which is
running and walking. Walking and running are good exercises. We must walk about 8 kilometers
every day to remain healthy. While working we move around a lot and therefore this app can
count the steps.
Walking is the easiest way to burn calories and keep your body in good shape. With this app you
can count the calories burnt in real time as you walk or run.
Water is essential for good health. One must drink at least 8 glasses of water every day. So, this
app also keeps record of the number of glasses of water consumed throughout the day. It
measures the amount of water intake in milliliters also.
Caffeine is not good for health but it is a stress buster. People tend to consume a lot of caffeine
during work. To cut down on caffeine intake, you can keep a record of the amount of caffeine
consumed daily in milligrams and cups.
This app updates and aware the people with health issues, latest research articles by renowned
doctors and physicians. You can get access to 30+ articles at a one time. Fresh articles are served
every hour.</string>
</resources>